Guide to the George Ellery Hale Papers HaleGE
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- Director's Files of the Mount Wilson Observatory, 1900–1926; 10; 11 linear feet (Tape HaleGE_02, Carton 2, Reel 81–100, Carton 4)
  - Rev. A. L. Cortie, 1907–1922; HaleGE_10_00_153_16; 99 pages (Box 153, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 85, frames 1138 to 1237.
  - Cooper Hewitt Electric Company, 1921; HaleGE_10_00_153_17; 10 pages (Box 153, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 85, frames 1238 to 1248.
  - A. Cotton, 1909–1910; HaleGE_10_00_153_18; 27 pages (Box 153, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 85, frames 1249 to 1276.
  - Couple-Gear Freight-Wheel, 1905–1908; HaleGE_10_00_153_19; 43 pages (Box 153, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 85, frames 1277 to 1326.
  - Heber D. Curtis, 1912–1919; HaleGE_10_00_153_20; 21 pages (Box 153, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 85, frames 1327 to 1348.
  - R. H. Curtis, 1909–1920; HaleGE_10_00_153_21; 18 pages (Box 153, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 85, frames 1349 to 1368.
  - Cramer Dry Plate Company, 1907–1916; HaleGE_10_00_153_22; 16 pages (Box 153, Folder 22)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 20 to 35.
  - C: Miscellaneous, 1904–1920; HaleGE_10_00_153_23; 215 pages (Box 153, Folder 23)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 36 to 249.
  - Arthur L. Day, 1906–1920; HaleGE_10_00_153_24; 38 pages (Box 153, Folder 24)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 250 to 287.
  - Frank C. Dennett, 1910–1912; HaleGE_10_00_153_25; 26 pages (Box 153, Folder 25)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 288 to 314.
  - H. Deslandres, 1904–1909; HaleGE_10_00_153_26; 11 pages (Box 153, Folder 26)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 315 to 326.
  - The Dictaphone, 1912; HaleGE_10_00_153_27; 6 pages (Box 153, Folder 27)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 327 to 333.
  - Dominion Astrophysical Observatory, 1913–1920; HaleGE_10_00_153_28; 57 pages (Box 153, Folder 28)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 334 to 392.
  - C. L. Doolittle, 1905; HaleGE_10_00_154_01; 9 pages (Box 154, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 393 to 402.
  - A. E. Douglas, 1907–1918; HaleGE_10_00_154_02; 47 pages (Box 154, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 403 to 450.
  - W. Geoffrey Duffield, 1907–1915; HaleGE_10_00_154_03; 54 pages (Box 154, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 451 to 504.
  - Ducommun Hardware Company, 1909–1914; HaleGE_10_00_154_04; 24 pages (Box 154, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 505 to 529.
  - J. C. Duncan, 1911–1920; HaleGE_10_00_154_05; 27 pages (Box 154, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 530 to 557.
  - Gano Dunn, 1919; HaleGE_10_00_154_06; 31 pages (Box 154, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 558 to 589.
  - F. W. Dyson, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_154_07; 20 pages (Box 154, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 590 to 610.
  - D: Miscellaneous, 1901–1920; HaleGE_10_00_154_08; 52 pages (Box 154, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 611 to 663.
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1911–1920; HaleGE_10_00_154_09; 36 pages (Box 154, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 664 to 701.
  - G. Eberhard, 1905–1908; HaleGE_10_00_154_10; 18 pages (Box 154, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 702 to 720.
  - A. S. Eddington, 1914–1920; HaleGE_10_00_154_11; 37 pages (Box 154, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 721 to 758.
  - Eimer and Amend, 1905–1910; HaleGE_10_00_154_12; 26 pages (Box 154, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 759 to 785.
  - Ferdinand Ellerman, 1908–1923; HaleGE_10_00_154_13; 54 pages (Box 154, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 786 to 840.
  - Charles F. Elmes Engineering Works, 1911; HaleGE_10_00_154_14; 19 pages (Box 154, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 841 to 860.
  - R. Emden, 1908; HaleGE_10_00_154_15; 3 pages (Box 154, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 861 to 864.
  - A. H. Emery, 1911–1913; HaleGE_10_00_154_16; 14 pages (Box 154, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 865 to 879.
  - Encyclopedia Americana, 1919; HaleGE_10_00_154_17; 15 pages (Box 154, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 880 to 895.
  - Paul Epstein, 1913–1921; HaleGE_10_00_154_18; 23 pages (Box 154, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 896 to 919.
  - Estimates, 1912–1916; HaleGE_10_00_154_19 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - J. Evershed, 1905–1915; HaleGE_10_00_154_20; 71 pages (Box 154, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 920 to 991.
  - Exhibition San Francisco, 1913–1914; HaleGE_10_00_154_21; 33 pages (Box 154, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 992 to 1025.
  - E: Miscellaneous, 1909–1917; HaleGE_10_00_154_22; 44 pages (Box 154, Folder 22)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 86, frames 1026 to 1071.
  - Charles Fabry, 1905–1913; HaleGE_10_00_154_23; 16 pages (Box 154, Folder 23)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 20 to 36.
  - Fairbanks, Morse and Company, 1905–1914; HaleGE_10_00_154_24; 100 pages (Box 154, Folder 24)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 37 to 138.
  - E. A. Fath, 1908–1913; HaleGE_10_00_154_25; 29 pages (Box 154, Folder 25)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 139 to 169.
  - Fore River Shipbuilding Corporation, 1912–1913; HaleGE_10_00_155_01; 250 pages (Box 155, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 170 to 419.
  - Fay and Scott, 1909; HaleGE_10_00_155_02; 13 pages (Box 155, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 420 to 433.
  - Camille Flammarion, 1910–1920; HaleGE_10_00_155_03; 19 pages (Box 155, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 434 to 453.
  - First National Bank, Pasadena, 1908–1914; HaleGE_10_00_155_04; 9 pages (Box 155, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 454 to 463.
  - U. S. Forest Service, 1909–1920; HaleGE_10_00_155_05; 40 pages (Box 155, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 464 to 505.
  - F. E. Fowle, 1910–1919; HaleGE_10_00_155_06; 25 pages (Box 155, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 506 to 530.
  - A. Fowler, 1906–1913; HaleGE_10_00_155_07; 85 pages (Box 155, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 531 to 616.
  - Philip Fox, 1904–1922; HaleGE_10_00_155_08; 110 pages (Box 155, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 617 to 728.
  - Frankford Arsenal, 1918; HaleGE_10_00_155_09; 15 pages (Box 155, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 729 to 744.
  - J. Franklin Adams, 1912; HaleGE_10_00_155_10; 4 pages (Box 155, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 745 to 749.
  - Fulton Engine Works, 1907–1912; HaleGE_10_00_155_11; 17 pages (Box 155, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 750 to 767.
  - Caroline E. Furness, 1911; HaleGE_10_00_155_12; 1 pages (Box 155, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 768 to 769.
  - French Plate Glass Companies, 1904–1913; HaleGE_10_00_155_13; 163 pages (Box 155, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 770 to 932.
  - F: Miscellaneous, 1905–1916; HaleGE_10_00_155_14; 93 pages (Box 155, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 87, frames 933 to 1022.
  - E. B. Frost, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_156_01; 764 pages (Box 156, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 88, frames 20 to 784.
  - Henry G. Gale, 1905–1921; HaleGE_10_00_156_02; 261 pages (Box 156, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 88, frames 785 to 1048.
  - General Electric Company, 1912–1920; HaleGE_10_00_156_03; 60 pages (Box 156, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 88, frames 1049 to 1110.
  - William Gaertner, 1905–1916; HaleGE_10_00_157_01; 164 pages (Box 157, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 88, frames 1111 to 1275.
  - F. G. Gibbs, 1913–1920; HaleGE_10_00_157_02; 33 pages (Box 157, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 20 to 53.
  - Walter M. Gilbert, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_157_03; 492 pages (Box 157, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 54 to 544.
  - Sir David Gill, 1911–1914; HaleGE_10_00_157_04; 23 pages (Box 157, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 545 to 568.
  - Graham-Burnham Company, 1915–1917; HaleGE_10_00_157_05; 11 pages (Box 157, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 569 to 580.
  - H. E. Gregory, 1921; HaleGE_10_00_157_06; 3 pages (Box 157, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 581 to 584.
  - William H. Guild and Company, 1909–1916; HaleGE_10_00_157_07; 22 pages (Box 157, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 585 to 607.
  - Gundlach-Manhattan Optical Company, 1909–1919; HaleGE_10_00_157_08; 15 pages (Box 157, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 608 to 623.
  - G: Miscellaneous, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_157_09; 150 pages (Box 157, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 624 to 775.
  - John G. Hagen, S.J., 1911–1921; HaleGE_10_00_158_01; 17 pages (Box 158, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 776 to 793.
  - George Ellery Hale, 1905–1925; HaleGE_10_00_158_02; 403 pages (Box 158, Folder 2–3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 794 to 1197.
  - J. Hargreaves, 1923; HaleGE_10_00_158_04; 1 pages (Box 158, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 1198 to 1199.
  - J. Hartman, 1903–1914; HaleGE_10_00_158_05; 61 pages (Box 158, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 1200 to 1261.
  - James Hartness, 1911–1916; HaleGE_10_00_158_06; 15 pages (Box 158, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 1262 to 1277.
  - Harvard College, 1913–1920; HaleGE_10_00_158_07; 26 pages (Box 158, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 89, frames 1278 to 1305.
  - B. Hasselberg, 1904–1908; HaleGE_10_00_158_08; 36 pages (Box 158, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 20 to 57.
  - C. S. Hastings, 1908–1909; HaleGE_10_00_158_09; 27 pages (Box 158, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 58 to 85.
  - F. Henroteau, 1917–1920; HaleGE_10_00_158_10; 21 pages (Box 158, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 86 to 108.
  - W. C. Heraeus, 1905–1906; HaleGE_10_00_158_11; 17 pages (Box 158, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 109 to 126.
  - Herschel Mirror, 1911–1922; HaleGE_10_00_158_12; 11 pages (Box 158, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 127 to 138.
  - Ejnar Hertzsprung, 1911–1921; HaleGE_10_00_158_13; 59 pages (Box 158, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 139 to 199.
  - A. Hilger, Ltd., 1905–1914; HaleGE_10_00_158_14; 99 pages (Box 158, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 200 to 299.
  - Arthur R. Hinks, 1910–1920; HaleGE_10_00_158_15; 9 pages (Box 158, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 300 to 309.
  - W. P. Hoge, 1914–1922; HaleGE_10_00_158_16; 85 pages (Box 158, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 310 to 396.
  - John D. Hooker, 1907–1908; HaleGE_10_00_159_01; 17 pages (Box 159, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 397 to 414.
  - Janet T. Howell, 1915–1917; HaleGE_10_00_159_02; 65 pages (Box 159, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 415 to 480.
  - Edwin P. Hubble, 1917–1919; HaleGE_10_00_159_03; 9 pages (Box 159, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 481 to 490.
  - W. J. Humphreys, 1906–1920; HaleGE_10_00_159_04; 17 pages (Box 159, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 491 to 508.
  - Myron Hunt, 1905–1918; HaleGE_10_00_159_05; 101 pages (Box 159, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 509 to 612.
  - W. J. Hussey, 1903–1920; HaleGE_10_00_159_06; 34 pages (Box 159, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 613 to 647.
  - Charles L. Hutchinson, 1905; HaleGE_10_00_159_07; 22 pages (Box 159, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 648 to 670.
  - H: Miscellaneous, 1904–1922; HaleGE_10_00_159_08; 245 pages (Box 159, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 671 to 916.
  - Ilford, Ltd., 1909; HaleGE_10_00_159_09; 1 pages (Box 159, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 917 to 918.
  - Imperial College of Science and Technology, 1921; HaleGE_10_00_159_10; 2 pages (Box 159, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 919 to 921.
  - Institute Oceanographique Monaco, 1919; HaleGE_10_00_159_11; 2 pages (Box 159, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 922 to 924.
  - Insurance, 1907–1920; HaleGE_10_00_159_12; 64 pages (Box 159, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 925 to 989.
  - Insurance and Annuity Association, 1919–1920; HaleGE_10_00_159_13; 40 pages (Box 159, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 990 to 1031.
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1908–1915; HaleGE_10_00_159_14; 13 pages (Box 159, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 90, frames 1032 to 1046.
  - International Acheson Graphite Company, 1906–1910; HaleGE_10_00_159_15; 26 pages (Box 159, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 20 to 46.
  - International Encyclopedia, 1914–1916; HaleGE_10_00_159_16; 35 pages (Box 159, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 47 to 82.
  - International Solar Union, 1905; HaleGE_10_00_159_17; 221 pages (Box 159, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 83 to 304.
  - Interstate Commerce, 1910–1916; HaleGE_10_00_159_18; 43 pages (Box 159, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 305 to 348.
  - George S. Isham, 1917; HaleGE_10_00_159_19; 7 pages (Box 159, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 349 to 356.
  - I: Miscellaneous, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_159_20; 30 pages (Box 159, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 357 to 387.
  - Harold Jacoby, 1913–1920; HaleGE_10_00_160_01; 13 pages (Box 160, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 388 to 400.
  - Clement Jacomini, 1915–1916; HaleGE_10_00_160_02; 63 pages (Box 160, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 401 to 462.
  - Jules Jansen, 1905–1921; HaleGE_10_00_160_03; 75 pages (Box 160, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 463 to 535.
  - J. H. Jeans, 1917–1922; HaleGE_10_00_160_04; 14 pages (Box 160, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 536 to 549.
  - C. E. Jewell, 1903–1907; HaleGE_10_00_160_05; 14 pages (Box 160, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 550 to 563.
  - N. Johanssen, 1917–1921; HaleGE_10_00_160_06; 41 pages (Box 160, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 564 to 604.
  - George D. Jones, 1908–1920; HaleGE_10_00_160_07; 15 pages (Box 160, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 605 to 619.
  - Alfred J. Joy, 1915–1918; HaleGE_10_00_160_08; 18 pages (Box 160, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 620 to 637.
  - W. H. Julius, 1904–1921; HaleGE_10_00_160_09; 171 pages (Box 160, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 638 to 808.
  - J: Miscellaneous, 1905–1922; HaleGE_10_00_160_10; 91 pages (Box 160, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 809 to 899.
  - J. C. Kapteyn, 1921–1922; HaleGE_10_00_160_11; 21 pages (Box 160, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 900 to 920.
  - Rev. D. Kennedy, 1908–1909; HaleGE_10_00_160_12; 15 pages (Box 160, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 921 to 935.
  - N. A. Kent, 1903–1915; HaleGE_10_00_160_13; 55 pages (Box 160, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 936 to 990.
  - F. E. Kester, 1912–1914; HaleGE_10_00_160_14; 8 pages (Box 160, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 991 to 998.
  - Arthur S. King, 1907–1921; HaleGE_10_00_160_15; 155 pages (Box 160, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 999 to 1153.
  - William H. Knight, 1909–1912; HaleGE_10_00_160_16; 17 pages (Box 160, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 1154 to 1170.
  - Peter Paul Koch, 1912–1913; HaleGE_10_00_160_17; 31 pages (Box 160, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 1171 to 1201.
  - Kodaikanal and Madras Observatory, 1922–1923; HaleGE_10_00_160_18; 4 pages (Box 160, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 1202 to 1205.
  - G. W. Koiner, 1911; HaleGE_10_00_160_19; 10 pages (Box 160, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 1206 to 1215.
  - Arnold Kohlschutter, 1911–1916; HaleGE_10_00_160_20; 62 pages (Box 160, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 1216 to 1277.
  - K: Miscellaneous, 1904–1917; HaleGE_10_00_160_21; 90 pages (Box 160, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 91, frames 1278 to 1371.
  - Andrew L. Lawson, 1921; HaleGE_10_00_161_01; 9 pages (Box 161, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 92, frames 19 to 28.
  - Leeds and Northrup, 1909–1920; HaleGE_10_00_161_02; 18 pages (Box 161, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 92, frames 29 to 47.
  - E. P. Lewis, 1915; HaleGE_10_00_161_03; 17 pages (Box 161, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 92, frames 48 to 65.
  - Gilbert N. Lewis, 1915; HaleGE_10_00_161_04; 4 pages (Box 161, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 92, frames 66 to 70.
  - A. O. Louschner, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_161_05; 86 pages (Box 161, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 92, frames 71 to 157.
  - Bertil Lindblad, 1920–1923; HaleGE_10_00_161_06; 42 pages (Box 161, Folder 6)